pressnews.biz 2019-10-06

# PRBiz - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

PRRESSNEWS.BIZ(PRBiz) is a professional website providing press release distribution service on behalf of our customers. Once you submit a press release on our site, we will distribute your press release in its entirety, including personal information (Your email will be shown as ***@sample.com for spam protection, though it also allows readers to contact you to deliver important information.) filled in your media contact information. Your submission of press releases through our system indicates consent with this policy. 

Collected Information

* PRBiz collects personal information in situations such as, but not limited to, when you register with PRBiz, when you use our products or services.  
* When you register we ask for information such as, your name, address, email address. Once you register with PRBiz and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.  
* PRBiz collects information about you from the press releases you have submitted, such as, but not limited to, your name, email address, phone number, industry, company name, company website.   
* PRBiz does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 may not use PRBiz and parents or legal guardians may not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use on their behalf. 

Third-Party Sites

PRBiz does not share our users' information with third parties. The only time information is shared is when our customers submit their contact information during distribution of their press release. The information obtained at the time you register with PRBiz is used to keep you up to date of our services and web site. It is necessary to register an account with us to track your press releases and make future modifications or enhancements to your release. The information you provide is not shared with outside organizations. This information is kept confidential. 

Google Analytics

This Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service of Google Inc.   
For more information on terms of use and data protection/privacy, please see [www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html). 

Security

PRBiz takes your privacy seriously and bears responsibility for protecting the data that you provide us in the normal course of interacting with our site. In order to maintain the confidentiality of all information you provide to us we strictly adhere to the following Security Policy outlined below. 

**User Information:**  
User account information that you provide (such as your email address, address, phone number, passwords, credit card or payment information, etc.) is held in strict confidence and will not be sold or rented to the 3rd parties, but will be used for the purposes of providing services described on this website. However, if the user was reported illegal, copyright infringement, Private and confidential personal information, Libelous, defamatory, threats content, we have the rights to gives the basic information to the judge, court, or the reporter. 

**Email:**  
a. We'll never share or sell your email address to a third party Uses;  
b. System updates. This item includes action required to activate membership, your press release stats, release & update notification etc. (Irregular delivery, if it is necessary.)  
c. Free-Press-release.com from time to time may periodically send out newsletters to our registered members for the purpose of updating them of further enhancements, inclusions or changes to our system. If you do not wish to receive these update notices, please email us to have you removed from our newsletter.

**Links**  
Attention Journalists & Publishers; Our Reprint Policies:  
a.For other media, please acknowledge  
b.For internet use, you must link back to the active original press release on PRBiz  
Article Source:PRBiz 

Funds Policy

*You shall pay all fees or charges to your account in accordance with the fees or charges, and services in effect at the time a fee or charge is due and payable. All payment obligations are noncancelable and all amounts paid are nonrefundable. You must provide Free-Press-release.com with valid credit card information to use the Service. PRBiz reserves the right to modify its fees and charges and to introduce new charges at any time.  
*You shall be responsible for payment of all such taxes, levies, or duties. If you believe your funds are incorrect, you must contact us in writing within 60 days.  
*You agree to provide PRBiz with complete and accurate funds and contact information. If the contact information you have provided is false or fraudulent, PRBiz reserves the right to terminate your access to the Service in addition to any other legal remedies.  

Content Policy

A: Pornographic, adult or mature content not allowed.  
B: Libelous, defamatory, threats or hate promoting content not allowed.  
C: Copyright violations not allowed.  
D: Private and confidential personal information not allowed.  
E: Spamming, hacking, cracking, malware or viruses or related content not allowed.  
F: Content that related to video downloading or converting are not allowed, suspicious content will be rejected or deleted.   
G: No content that is illegal, promotes illegal activity, or infringes on the legal rights of others.  

Policy Changes Statement

PRBiz has the right to change the policy at any time. Policy changes will be posted in time to notify you and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. To keep up-to-date with PRBiz's policy, please check this page periodically.
